Ted Koppel Collection
Ted Koppel Collection
- Nightline, 1980-2005
  - 1989
    - Nightline: Former KGB, CIA Leaders Meet, 09/28/1989; koppel_nl89092801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Protecting Performing Animals, 09/29/1989; koppel_nl89092901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: New Identical Twins Study, 10/02/1989; koppel_nl89100201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Coup Against Noriega Fails, 10/03/1989; koppel_nl89100301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: US Role in Panama Coup Attempt/East German Refugee Exodus Update, 10/04/1989; koppel_nl89100401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Jim Bakker Found Guilty, 10/05/1989; koppel_nl89100501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: East Germans Mark 40th Anniversary, 10/06/1989; koppel_nl89100601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Galileo Launch in Court Over Safety Issue, 10/09/1989; koppel_nl89100901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Revisiting the Aftermath of Hurricane Hugo, 10/10/1989; koppel_nl89101001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: The Politics of Abortion, 10/11/1989; koppel_nl89101101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Medellin, Colombia, 10/12/1989; koppel_nl89101201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Stock Market Falls 190 Points, 10/13/1989; koppel_nl89101301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Wall Street Seesaw: Worst Now Over?, 10/16/1989; koppel_nl89101601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: San Francisco Earthquake [EARLY EDITION], 10/17/1989; koppel_nl89101701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: San Francisco Earthquake [LATE EDITION], 10/17/1989; koppel_nl89101702; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: California Earthquake Aftermath, 10/18/1989; koppel_nl89101801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: California Earthquake Update/Kentucky Floods [EARLY EDITION], 10/19/1989; koppel_nl89101901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Bay Area: Pulling Together After The Quake, 10/20/1989; koppel_nl89102001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Ronald Reagan Pays Paid Visit to Japan, 10/23/1989; koppel_nl89102301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Jim Bakker Sentenced to 45 Years/Inside Oakland Freeway Rescue Effort, 10/24/1989; koppel_nl89102401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Cholesterol Controversy, 10/25/1989; koppel_nl89102501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: World Series Resumes Tomorrow, 10/26/1989; koppel_nl89102601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Bay Area Residents: How Are They?, 10/27/1989; koppel_nl89102701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Gays in the Military, 10/30/1989; koppel_nl89103001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Worldwide Striving for Democracy, 10/31/1989; koppel_nl89103101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Nicaraguans End Cease-Fire, 11/01/1989; koppel_nl89110101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: McMartin Child Abuse Case Goes to Jury, 11/02/1989; koppel_nl89110201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Iran Hostage Crisis 10th Anniversary, 11/03/1989; koppel_nl89110301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Catholic Bishops Mull Just Saying No to Condom Use for AIDS Prevention, 11/06/1989; koppel_nl89110601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Elections Make History/East Germany, 11/07/1989; koppel_nl89110701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: East German Government Reforms?, 11/08/1989; koppel_nl89110801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: A Crack in the Berlin Wall, 11/09/1989; koppel_nl89110901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Berlin Wall/East German Saga Continues, 11/10/1989; koppel_nl89111001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: New East German Premier, Protests, 11/13/1989; koppel_nl89111301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Lech Walesa Interview, 11/14/1989; koppel_nl89111401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Deadly Tornadoes Hit South, Midwest, 11/15/1989; koppel_nl89111501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Jesuit Priests Killed in El Salvador, 11/16/1989; koppel_nl89111601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Yuri Dubinin Interview, 11/17/1989; koppel_nl89111701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: Anabolic Steroid Use, 11/20/1989; koppel_nl89112001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 149)
    - Nightline: El Salvador Rebels Seize Hotel, 11/21/1989; koppel_nl89112101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: The Keating Savings and Loan Case: Influence for Sale?, 11/22/1989; koppel_nl89112201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: A Thanksgiving of Hope, 11/23/1989; koppel_nl89112301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Racism and Rock, 11/24/1989; koppel_nl89112401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Rapid Change in Czechoslovakia, 11/27/1989; koppel_nl89112701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Living Donor Liver Transplant Done in US, 11/28/1989; koppel_nl89112801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Pro-Democracy Movement in Burma, 11/29/1989; koppel_nl89112901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Fighting Continues in Philippines Despite US Intervention, 12/01/1989; koppel_nl89120101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: NCAA Football Play-Off Debate, 12/04/1989; koppel_nl89120401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Philippines Update, 12/05/1989; koppel_nl89120501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: The Drug Battle in Colombia Escalates, 12/06/1989; koppel_nl89120601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Baltic Troubles for Gorbachev, 12/07/1989; koppel_nl89120701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Naval Investigative Service Under Scrutiny, 12/08/1989; koppel_nl89120801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Bush Sends Envoys to China Despite Ban, 12/11/1989; koppel_nl89121101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Open Adoption, 12/12/1989; koppel_nl89121201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Japanese Investment in The United States, 12/13/1989; koppel_nl89121301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: The Fate of Vietnam's Boat People, 12/14/1989; koppel_nl89121401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: American Novels, 12/15/1989; koppel_nl89121501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Divorce Wars, 12/18/1989; koppel_nl89121801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Mail Bombs Kill Two, Threaten Others Involved with Civil Rights, 12/19/1989; koppel_nl89121901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: United States Invades Panama, 12/20/1989; koppel_nl89122001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: More Fighting in Panama, But No Noriega, 12/21/1989; koppel_nl89122101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Updates from Panama and Romania, 12/22/1989; koppel_nl89122201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Christmas in Panama and Romania, 12/25/1989; koppel_nl89122501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Romania Struggles for Democratic Change, 12/26/1989; koppel_nl89122601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: US and Vatican Struggle Over Noriega, 12/27/1989; koppel_nl89122701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Independent Living for the Disabled/Panama Update, 12/28/1989; koppel_nl89122801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: 1990 Predictions, 12/29/1989; koppel_nl89122901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
  - 1990
    - Nightline: SMU Returns to Football/Panama Update, 01/01/1990; koppel_nl90010101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Who Will Pay for US Policy in Panama?, 01/02/1990; koppel_nl90010201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Noriega Turns Himself In, Is Flown to US, 01/03/1990; koppel_nl90010301; tape mislabeled: episode not on tape
    - Nightline: After Panama, Anti-Drug Military Options, 01/04/1990; koppel_nl90010401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Jon Parker Case: Clean Needles to Prevent AIDS, 01/05/1990; koppel_nl90010501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Boston's Stuart Murder-Suicide Case, 01/08/1990; koppel_nl90010801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Khmer Rouge on Offensive in Cambodia, 01/09/1990; koppel_nl90010901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: A Romanian Exile Returns, 01/10/1990; koppel_nl90011001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Gorbachev in Lithuania Amidst Protests, 01/11/1990; koppel_nl90011101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Caller ID, 01/12/1990; koppel_nl90011201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Ethnic Unrest in the USSR, 01/15/1990; koppel_nl90011501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Where Should Foreign Aid Go?, 01/16/1990; koppel_nl90011601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Does Oat Bran Work?, 01/17/1990; koppel_nl90011701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: DC Mayor Arrested/McMartin Trial Verdict, 01/18/1990; koppel_nl90011801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: DC Mayor Marion Barry's Arrest, 01/19/1990; koppel_nl90011901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Turmoil in Soviet Azerbaijan and Armenia, 01/22/1990; koppel_nl90012201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: The Media and Fair Trials, 01/23/1990; koppel_nl90012301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: NFL Drug Testing Controversy/Avianca Crash on Long Island, 01/25/1990; koppel_nl90012501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Violent Hate Crimes Against Gays, 01/26/1990; koppel_nl90012601
    - Nightline: The Defense Budget: Under Fire, 01/29/1990; koppel_nl90012901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Homeless Panhandlers, 01/30/1990; koppel_nl90013001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Bush's State of The Presidency, 01/31/1990; koppel_nl90013101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Aspen's Fur Fight, 02/01/1990; koppel_nl90020101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Mandela to Be Freed, ANC Legalized, 02/02/1990; koppel_nl90020201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Gorbachev's Radical Proposals for Soviets, 02/05/1990; koppel_nl90020501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Docudramas and Re-Creations, 02/06/1990; koppel_nl90020601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: In South Africa, 02/07/1990; koppel_nl90020701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: What Happens After Mandela is Free?, 02/08/1990; koppel_nl90020801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: The South African Press, 02/09/1990; koppel_nl90020901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Mandela's First Day of Freedom, 02/12/1990; koppel_nl90021201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: South African President FW De Klerk, 02/13/1990; koppel_nl90021301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: A Town Meeting in South Africa [PART 1], 02/14/1990; koppel_nl90021401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: A Town Meeting in South Africa [PART 2], 02/14/1990; koppel_nl90021402; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Speaking with Nelson Mandela, 02/15/1990; koppel_nl90021501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: The Misery Drugs Bring to Colombia, 02/16/1990; koppel_nl90021601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Prenuptial Agreements, 02/19/1990; koppel_nl90021901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Breaking the Gender Barrier at VMI, 02/20/1990; koppel_nl90022001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Hagersville, Ontario Tire Fire Disaster, 02/21/1990; koppel_nl90022101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: The Andy Rooney Controversy, 02/22/1990; koppel_nl90022201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Nicaraguan Elections, 02/23/1990; koppel_nl90022301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Chamorro Wins Nicaraguan Election, 02/26/1990; koppel_nl90022601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Smoking: Getting to be a Real Drag, 02/27/1990; koppel_nl90022701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Japanese Cars: Really Better?, 02/28/1990; koppel_nl90022801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: The CIA: Down and Dirty with Noriega, 03/01/1990; koppel_nl90030101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: The Major League Baseball Lockout, 03/02/1990; koppel_nl90030201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Malathion Danger Controversy, 03/05/1990; koppel_nl90030501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Philippine President Corazon Aquino, 03/06/1990; koppel_nl90030601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Are Big Bucks Ruining College Athletics?, 03/07/1990; koppel_nl90030701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Israelis Dragging Feet in Peace Process, 03/08/1990; koppel_nl90030801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Electromagnetic Field Hazards, 03/09/1990; koppel_nl90030901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Salk AIDS Vaccine Test Controversy, 03/12/1990; koppel_nl90031201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Children with AIDS, 03/13/1990; koppel_nl90031301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Libya Chemical Plant Fire/Castro's Future, 03/14/1990; koppel_nl90031401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: Iraqis Kill British-Based Journalist, 03/15/1990; koppel_nl90031501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 150)
    - Nightline: US Postal Service: More for Less?, 03/16/1990; koppel_nl90031601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: East German Conservatives Win, 03/19/1990; koppel_nl90031901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Ovarian Cancer, 03/20/1990; koppel_nl90032001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Boston's Gardner Museum Art Theft, 03/21/1990; koppel_nl90032101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Behind the Scenes of "A Chorus Line", 03/22/1990; koppel_nl90032201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: The 1990 Census, 03/23/1990; koppel_nl90032301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: The Academy Awards/Tension in Lithuania, 03/26/1990; koppel_nl90032601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Soviet-Lithuanian Tensions Increase, 03/27/1990; koppel_nl90032701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Protecting Rape Victims' Identities: Helping or Hurting?, 03/28/1990; koppel_nl90032801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Idaho Potato Boycott, 03/29/1990; koppel_nl90032901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Sneakers: Buying Basketball Players?/Hank Gathers' Legacy, 03/30/1990; koppel_nl90033001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Tax Revolt in England, 04/02/1990; koppel_nl90040201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Life on Death Row, 04/03/1990; koppel_nl90040301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Ethiopian Civil War Causing New Famine, 04/04/1990; koppel_nl90040401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Nebraska Nuclear Waste Dump Fight, 04/05/1990; koppel_nl90040501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Teenage Abortion and Parental Notification, 04/06/1990; koppel_nl90040601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: The Hubble Telescope Launch, 04/09/1990; koppel_nl90040901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Mapplethorpe: "Obscene" in Cincinnati?, 04/10/1990; koppel_nl90041001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Ryan White, 1971-1990, 04/11/1990; koppel_nl90041101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: America's Infant Mortality Crisis, 04/12/1990; koppel_nl90041201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Income Tax, 04/13/1990; koppel_nl90041301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Cheating in College, 04/16/1990; koppel_nl90041601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Chai Ling, Chinese Student Leader, 04/17/1990; koppel_nl90041701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: San Francisco's Earthquakes, 04/18/1990; koppel_nl90041801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Tough Choices in Lithuania, 04/19/1990; koppel_nl90041901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: The Hostages: Life in Captivity, 04/20/1990; koppel_nl90042001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: New Development in the Hostage Situation, 04/23/1990; koppel_nl90042301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Akio Morita of Sony, 04/24/1990; koppel_nl90042401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Ethnic, Nationalist Breaks in the USSR, 04/25/1990; koppel_nl90042501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Washington's Diminishing Importance, 04/27/1990; koppel_nl90042701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Second US Hostage Freed in Eight Days, 04/30/1990; koppel_nl90043001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: May Day 1990, 05/01/1990; koppel_nl90050101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Child Labor Abuse in the United States, 05/02/1990; koppel_nl90050201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Kilauea's Lava Torches Kalapana, Hawaii, 05/03/1990; koppel_nl90050301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: 20 Years After Kent State, 05/04/1990; koppel_nl90050401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Bush Breaking Word on Tax Promise?, 05/08/1990; koppel_nl90050801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Floods Hit US South Central Region, 05/09/1990; koppel_nl90050901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Will Marion Barry Rise Again?, 05/10/1990; koppel_nl90051001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Entertainment or Bad Taste?, 05/11/1990; koppel_nl90051101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: The Lincoln Savings and Loan-Keating Debacle, 05/14/1990; koppel_nl90051401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Racial Tensions in New York City, 05/15/1990; koppel_nl90051501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Sammy Davis, Jr./Jim Henson, 05/16/1990; koppel_nl90051601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Montana Cult, 05/17/1990; koppel_nl90051701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Women's-Only Colleges, 05/18/1990; koppel_nl90051801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: New Violence Follows Murders of Palestinians by "Deranged" Israeli, 05/21/1990; koppel_nl90052101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Brazil: Documenting A History of Torture, 05/22/1990; koppel_nl90052201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Berendzen Pleads Guilty to Obscene Calls, 05/23/1990; koppel_nl90052301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Movie Ratings System Controversy, 05/24/1990; koppel_nl90052401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Combating Drunk Drivers: What Works?, 05/25/1990; koppel_nl90052501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Gorbachev's Problems at Home, 05/28/1990; koppel_nl90052801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: From the Front Lines in Eritrea, 05/29/1990; koppel_nl90052901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: The Washington Summit, 05/30/1990; koppel_nl90053001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Soviet Journalists Discuss Changes in The Soviet Union, 05/31/1990; koppel_nl90053101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: The Summit Process/Mrs. Bush at Wellesley, 06/01/1990; koppel_nl90060101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Tiananmen Square: One Year Later, 06/04/1990; koppel_nl90060401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: A Losing Trump Hand?, 06/05/1990; koppel_nl90060501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Physician-Assisted Suicide in Terminally Ill Patients, 06/06/1990; koppel_nl90060601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Why Won't Louisiana Parole Wilbert Rideau?, 06/07/1990; koppel_nl90060701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Biting the Bullet at the NRA, 06/08/1990; koppel_nl90060801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: How is Obscenity Defined?, 06/11/1990; koppel_nl90061101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Summertime Movie Blitz, 06/12/1990; koppel_nl90061201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Liberia's Brutal Civil War, 06/13/1990; koppel_nl90061301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: New Troubles in Romania and Bulgaria, 06/14/1990; koppel_nl90061401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Family Leave Faces "Pro-Family" Bush Veto, 06/15/1990; koppel_nl90061501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: The War on Gang War, 06/18/1990; koppel_nl90061801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Jailing Pregnant Drug Users: Does it Help or Hurt?, 06/19/1990; koppel_nl90061901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: International AIDS Conference in San Francisco, 06/20/1990; koppel_nl90062001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - 06/21/1990, see: The Koppel Report: A Town Meeting with Nelson Mandela
    - Nightline: Earthquake in Iran, 06/22/1990; koppel_nl90062201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: The Passive Smoking Controversy, 06/25/1990; koppel_nl90062501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: The Iran Earthquake Relief, 06/26/1990; koppel_nl90062601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Foster Care in Crisis, 06/27/1990; koppel_nl90062701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: The Barry Video: A Case of Entrapment?, 06/28/1990; koppel_nl90062801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: The Southwest's Firestorm Emergency, 06/29/1990; koppel_nl90062901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Excommunication of Pro-Choice Catholics, 07/02/1990; koppel_nl90070201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Extremes in Soviet Life, 07/03/1990; koppel_nl90070301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Celebrating The Fourth of July, 07/04/1990; koppel_nl90070401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: World Cup Soccer Fever, 07/05/1990; koppel_nl90070501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Texas Reporter Jailed for Protecting Sources, 07/06/1990; koppel_nl90070601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Louisiana Abortion Bill Struggle, 07/09/1990; koppel_nl90070901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: What's Wrong With NASA?, 07/10/1990; koppel_nl90071001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Ongoing Problems at The RTC, 07/11/1990; koppel_nl90071101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: New York's Zodiac Killer, 07/12/1990; koppel_nl90071201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Calling Baseball's Play-by-Play, 07/13/1990; koppel_nl90071301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: An Interview with King Hussein of Jordan, 07/16/1990; koppel_nl90071601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: The Savings and Loan Scandal and the Fall Elections, 07/17/1990; koppel_nl90071701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: The Perfect Baby: A Follow-Up, 07/18/1990; koppel_nl90071801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: The Resurrection of Richard Nixon, 07/19/1990; koppel_nl90071901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Supreme Court Justice William Brennan Resigns, 07/20/1990; koppel_nl90072001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 151)
    - Nightline: Bush Names Supreme Court Nominee, 07/23/1990; koppel_nl90072301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 152)
    - Nightline: The Crash of United Flight 232: A Year Later, 07/24/1990; koppel_nl90072401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 152)